Fowler C. West papers, Inclusive: 1964-2009, Bulk: 1965-1993
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Commodity Futures Trading Commission (CFTC), 1975-1993; 2
  - Subjects, 1982-1991; 11
    - Financial Products Advisory Committee Minutes, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Financial Products Advisory Committee Minutes, 1989 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Financial Products Advisory Committee Minutes, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Floor Broker Registration, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Foreign Bank Assessment of Certain BCCI Activities in the US, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Foreign Futures Articles, 1986-1988 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Fraud, Articles, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Fraud, California, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Fraud Cases, Dominelli, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Fraud Cases, Feldman and Martinson, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Fraud Cases, F.G. Hunter and Associates, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Fraud Cases, First Manhattan Commodities Corp., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Fraud Cases, Intercontinental Commodity Advisors, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Fraud Cases, Lowe, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Fraud Cases, Modoc Trading Group, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Fraud Cases, National Century Financial Corp, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Fraud Cases, National City Trading Corp., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Fraud Cases, National Coal Exchange, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Fraud Cases, Quinn and Co., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Fraud Cases, Regal commodities, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Fraud Cases, Rosenthal and Co., 1984 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Fraud Cases, Sorkin, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Fraud Cases, Vero Beach Accumulation Fund, 1984 (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Fraud Cases, Bullion Reserve of N. America, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Fraud Cases, International Silver Bullion Exchange Group, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Fraud Cases, Investment Metals International, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Fraud Cases, Oxborrow, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Fraud Cases, Murlas Commodities, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Fraud Cases, Hutton, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Fraud Cases, McVey Whitney Company, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Fraud Cases, Nelson Ghun and Associates, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Fraud Cases, Saxe v. E.F. Hutton, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Fraud, Risk Disclosure, 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Fraud, Securities and Commodities, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Fraud, Sustainability, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Fraud, Telemarketing, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Fry v. CFTC Respondent Brief, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Futures and Common Stock Margins, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Futures Funds and Price Volatility, 1896 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Futures Industry Association, 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Futures Markets on World Economy, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Futures Market Reform, 1988-1990 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Futures Market Regulation, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Futures Market Sales Practice Oversight, 1991 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Futures Trading Act of 1978, Conference Report, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Futures Trading Act of 1982 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Futures Trading Articles, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Futures Trading Articles, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Futures Trading Articles, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Futures Trading Articles, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Futures Trading Oversight, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Futures Trading Practices Act of 1989 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Futures Trading, USDA Bulletin, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - GAO Report, Chicago Futures Market, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - GAO Report, Evaluations of October Market Break, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Garson v. CFTC, 1990 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Geldermann, Inc., CBOT v. CFTC, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Global Financial Markets and Automation Risk, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Globex, Limitation of Liability, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Government Securities Act of 1986, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Government Securities Brokers and Dealers, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Joint Report on the Government Securities Market, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Gramm, Wendy, 1989-1992 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Hedging, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Future Trading Articles, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Hedging Definition, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - High Yield, Non-Investment Grade Bonds, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - History, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Hybrid Financial Instruments, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Hybrid Financial Instruments, Statutory Interpretations, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Index Related Trading and Market Decline, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Inflation Causes and Consequences, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Inspector General Act, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - International Organization of Securities Commission (IOSCO), 1990 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Issues, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Intermarket Coordination, 1991-1992 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Intermarket Frontrunning, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Interagency Jurisdiction Arbitration Panel, CFTC-SEC, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Introducing Brokers, Registration, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Investment Fraud Task Force, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Kansas City Board of Trade, Audit Review, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Kansas City Board of Trade, Stock Market Crash, 1989 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Kansas City Board of Trade, Rule Enforcement Review, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Kirkland & Ellis, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Klejna, Dennis — Statement Before the Consumer, Commerce, and Monetary Affairs Subcommittee, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Kuwaiti Assets Control Regulations, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - A Legal and Economic Analysis of Manipulation in Futures Markets, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Leveraged Transactions, 1981-1982 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Leverage Contracts, 1982-1989 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Leverage Survey Appendix, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Leverage Transactions Report, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Livestock Futures Market by Large Hedgers, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - LIFFE/FTSE 100, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Livestock Futures Trading and Market Options, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Mandated Studies, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Managed Accounts, Bunched Order Executions, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Managed Futures Association, Commodity Pools, 1991 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Manipulation, Futures Market, 1984, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Manipulation, Commodities Market, 1982-1990 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Margins, 1982-1990 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Market Facts Inc., Options and Futures Traders, 1984 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Market Reform Act, 1990-1992 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Market Squabbles, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - MidAmerica Commodity Exchange (MACE), Soybean Meal Futures, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Minneapolis Grain Exchange, Syrup Futures, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Minneapolis Grain Exchange, Enforcement Review, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Attorney General, December Energy Crisis, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), General, 1985-1989 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Application Guide, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Arbitration System, 1985-1986 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Briefing, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Clearinghouse Press Conference, 1991 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Compliance, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Disciplinary Action, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Disciplinary Information Access Line (DIAL), 1991 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Meeting, 1985 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Registration, 1982 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Regulatory Report, 1986 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Registration Fitness Program, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Sales Practice Regulation Investigations and Education, 1985-1986 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - National Futures Association (NFA), Supervision of Telemarking Activities, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - National Treatment Study, 1991 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Natural Gas Futures Handbook, New York Metals Exchange, 1987 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - New Financial Instruments, 1990 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - News, General, 1982-1992 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - New York Cotton Exchange (NYCE), Citrus Associates and Frozen Concentrated Juice Futures, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - New York Cotton Exchange (NYCE), Cotlook World Cotton Futures and Options, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - New York Cotton Exchange (NYCE), Five Year US Treasury Notes Futures, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - New York Futures Exchange (NYFE), Commodity Research Bureau Futures Price Index, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), Platinum Futures, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), Residual Fuel Oil Futures, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), Regulatory Task Force Report and Recommendations, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), Statement, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), Sour Crude Oil Futures, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - New York Mercantile Exchange (NYMEX), Unleaded Gasoline-Crude Oil Spread Option, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), Market Volatility and Investor Confidence, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), Overview of Program Trading, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), Program Trading Impact on Financial Markets, 1987 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - New York Stock Exchange (NYSE), Testimony, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - North American Securities Administrators Association (NASAA), Commodity Pool Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - North American Securities Administrators Association (NASAA), Commodity Pool Guidelines, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - North American Securities Administrators Association (NASAA), Investor Alert, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - North American Securities Administrators Association (NASAA), Conference Preregistration, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Off-Exchange Taskforce Interpretive Letters, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Off-Exchange Transactions, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Office of the Inspector General Semi-Annual Report, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Office of the Postmaster General, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Office of Technology Assessment (OTA), Securities and Futures Market, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Oil Futures Since Iraq Invasion, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Options, General, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Option Contracts, 1981-1982 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Options PBOT Eurodollar Options, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Options Pilot Program, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Options Seminar, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Options Trading, 1986 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Options Trading, Farmers, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Osaka Securities Exchange, Stock Futures 50, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Osaka Securities Exchange, Nikkei Stok Average Futures, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Paine Webber, Northern Offer of Settlement, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Pension Plans in the Futures Market, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), Commodity Investment Fraud, 1982-1984 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), Commodities Futures Trading Litigation Seminar, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), Enforcement and Surveillance, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), NASAA/CFTC Cooperation, 1983-1984 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), Off-Exchange Fraud, 1980-1984 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), Offshore Banks and Companies, 1980-1984 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), Precious Metal Fraud, 1983-1984 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), South Florida Boiler Room Operations, 1984 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), State Enforcement Actions, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), User Fees, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Permanent Subcommittee on Investigations (PSI), West’s Notes, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia Board of Trade (PBOT), Australian Dollar Futures, 1987 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Philadelphia Board of Trade (PBOT), OTC Index Futures, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Presidential Task Force on Market Mechanisms, 1987-1988 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - President’s Private Sector Survey on Cost Control, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Price Limits, 1988 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Private Risk-Ratings for Exemptions from Federal Regulations, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings Bulletin, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Program Objectives, 2nd Quarter FY85, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Program Objectives, 3rd Quarter FY85, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Program Objectives, 4th Quarter FY85, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Program Objectives, 3rd Quarter FY87, 1984 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Program Objectives, 3rd Quarter FY89, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Program Objectives, 2nd Quarter FY90, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Program Objectives, 3rd Quarter FY90, 1990 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Program Trading, 1988-1989 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Purdy v. CFTC, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO), Hanbury Statement, 1987 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Racketeer Influenced and Corrupt Organizations Act (RICO), Notes, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Reauthorization Bill, 1982-1983 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Reauthorization Bill, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Audit Trail, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Correspondence, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Debate, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Futures Trading Act Draft, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Leverage Contracts, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Markups, House and Senate, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Testimony, Susan M. Phillips, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Statement of Differences, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Reauthorization Bill, 1990 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Reauthorization Bill, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Reauthorization Bill, Futures Trading Practices Act of 1992 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Reauthorization Recommendations, 1982 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Regulation of Futures Margins, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Regulator Advisory Coordination Committee (RACC), Progress Reports, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Regulator Advisory Coordination Committee (RACC), Report, 1991-1992 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Regulator Advisory Coordination Committee (RACC), Report and Recommendation, 1989 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Regulatory Review and Reform, 1992 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Reparations, Proposed Rules, 1982-1990 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Reparations, Rules, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Risk Management, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Rule 4.5, Exclusion form definition of Commodity Pool Operators, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Rule 4.7, Qualifying Pools and Clients, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - S & P 500, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Salomon Brothers, Expiration of Stock-Index Futures, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Salomon Brothers, Treasury Bond Activities, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Schroeder, Edmund, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Securities and Commodities Fraud Working Group, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Securities Act Amendments, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), 1989 Market Volatilities, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Articles, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Chairman on Japan, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Chairman Breeden, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Correspondence, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Government Securities Activities of Futures Commission Merchant, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - Jurisdiction, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Market Crash, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Order on Delta Government Option Corporation, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Policy, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Regulatory Coordination, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Report on Stock Activities, 1990-1991 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Stock Market Volatility Report, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Study of NYSE Trading, 1988 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Study of Trading and Economy, 1984 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Securities Exchange Commission (SEC), Trading Analysis of Oct. 13 and 16, 1989, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Securities Firms, Assessing Need to Regulate Financial Activities, 1992 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Securities Market Reform Act of 1988 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Securities Markets, “Chinese Walls” Standards, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Securities Regulation and Customer Protection Rule Oversight Procedures, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Securities Trading and National Market System Issues, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Self-Regulation, 1990 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Senate Bill, Intermarket Coordination, 1991 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Short Selling, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - Silver, Crisis of 1980, 1982-1988 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Silver, Chicago Board of Trade, 1979-1980, 1982 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Silver, Rosenthal Subcommittee, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Silver, Trading, 1989 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Soybean Futures, 1984-1985 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Speculation and Manipulation in the Futures Market, 1981 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Speculative Position Limits, 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Speculative Position Limits, Exemptions, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Speculative Position Limits, No-Action Position, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Stock Index Futures, Activity, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Stock Index Futures, Cash Market Activity, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Stock Index Futures, Issues, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Stock Index Futures, Review Trading, 1987 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Stock Market Crash, 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Stock Market Volatility, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Sunshine Act, Court Interpretation, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Swaps, Innovation and Vulnerability, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Swaps, Exemptions, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Swaps, Rules, 1989 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Task Group on Regulation of Financial Services, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Tin Industry, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Tokyo Stock Exchange, Topix Futures, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Trading Cards and Submission of Trading Records, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Trading Systems, Screen Based, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Transaction Fee Proposal, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Transactional Risk and Market Crashes, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, Election Party, 1974 October 2 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, Nomination of Officers, 1974 September 18 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, St. Patrick's Day, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - President's Report, 1974 May (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - 47th Anniversary Dinner Dance Program, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - 50th Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1964 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1965 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1966 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1967 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1969 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1970 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1972 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1973 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1974 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1976 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1977 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1978 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1979 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1981 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1982 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Ronald Reagan, 1982-1983 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - General, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Michael Unger, 1986 March 7 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1987 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1988 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1989 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - General, Invitations, Thank you, etc., 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Hyde Murray, 1998-2009 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Meri Carol Martens, 2009 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Baylor Men and Women of Merit Week, 1984 February 6-8 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Washington Internship Program Advisory Committee, 1986-1991 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Jimmy Carter Honorary Degree Decision, 1989-1993 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Robert T. Miller Steering Committee Correspondence, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Bulletins, 1974 January-December (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Complimentary Membership Letters (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Complimentary Membership Letters (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Complimentary Membership Letters (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Elections, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Man of the Year Hubert Humphrey Program, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - 34th Anniversary Man of the Year Edmund S. Muskie Program, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - 36th Anniversary Man of the Year Carl Albert Program, 1971 April 3 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - 37th Anniversary Man of the Year Spiro T. Agnew Program, 1972 April 15 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - 38th Anniversary Man of the Year John W. McCormack, 1973 April 7 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - 39th Anniversary Man of the Year Gerald Ford Program, 1974 May 4 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - 40th Anniversary Man of the Year Thomas E. Morgan Program, 1975 June 21 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - 41st Anniversary Man of the Year Robert H. Michel Program, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Man of the Year Daniel Flood, 1977 October 15 (Box 65, Folder 3)